[Bret] Disco? Dead. Don't do that.
Never that ever again.
The '80s are about fluidity.
It's all about being loose and the flow.
[♪ "Our Lips Are Sealed" plays]
All right. This is what I want you to do.
Learning to dance.
[stomps]
Super easy. Yeah?
It's all about being in your body. Yeah?
What is that?
It's Belinda Carlisle's trademark move.
I saw her do it at The Roxy.
Come on. Uh?
Come on. Get up, get up. Let's do it.
Try it. Try it in the mirror.
Hmm. Up.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't-- [sighs] I don't wanna do that.
It's kind of gay, don't you think?
You know what?
You know what's gonna work for you?
-Pocket dancing.
-Pocket dancing?
All you need is an oversized jacket.
And then you can be that guy, you know?
It's the life raft
for the uncoordinated man.
Who can accuse you of being stiff
when the whole point is to be stiff?
Look, I don't wanna do this!
I don't wanna go on some stupid dance show
and embarrass myself on television.
The entire situation is ludicrous,
but we don't really have a choice, do we?
Mr. Schaffer set the whole thing up.
You're just gonna have
to find a dance style that works for you.
[exhales] He's a really good dancer, man.
-Who is?
-Robert.
You saw him. Even when he's losing
his mind, he's got moves.
Susan's gonna wish she was dancing
with him instead of me.
And that will be the beginning of the end.
Susan loves you, Thom.
Yeah, and my dad loved my mom.
Until he left her for somebody better.
Robert isn't any better than you.
In fact, we don't even know
who Robert really is.
He's sophisticated.
He knows about sailboats
and garnishes and "Prowst."
It's… Proust, but I understand
why someone would say "Prowst."
I think he's gonna hurt her.
I feel it.
[♪ tense music plays]
I can't let that happen.
I'd do anything for her. To keep her safe,
to keep her with me.
-I'd--
-You'd kill for her.
I would.
I'm worried about you, Thom.
Ever since the other night
at the party with the crazy cult guy…
you've been acting strange.
What are you trying to say, Bret?
I don't know.
I just feel like there's something
going on that I don't know about.
Help me understand.
Hmm?
You can let me in.
I'm a friend.
I know.
I'm just stressed about the dance-off.
That's it.
Okay. All right.
Let's try something else.
Um… [sighs] Okay. I think…
[record player switch clicks]
…this is gonna be
a little more your speed.
Super simple. Robot.
[Steven] She's so romantic.
I don't think you can pull it off.
I mean, it's slutty, but it's good.
You can do that.
Ah. Pearls, pearls.
I mean, hair and fur.
What else do you want?
[Debbie] I don't know, Steven. [sighs]
I need to stand out.
I… want drama.
Trust me.
Pastels are where the '80s are headed.
But… [slaps table] …you don't want someone
with vision styling you for the show,
then you can just
walk yourself into a Sears
and tell those pug dogs
at the counter to hose you down
with all the brown corduroy they've got.
[Susan chortles, laughs]
Here. This is it.
Claude Montana. Headpiece, shoulders,
waist, peplum, harem. Perfect.
No.
[scoffs lightly]
[clears throat]
Steven, what is Cha Cha doing
in your purse?
-To remind you what's at stake.
-That is my Dance Off! competition.
I am aware of that.
And she has style, which you don't.
And you need to get a heap of it.
She's trash. She's poor.
Compare, then flair.
Okay, seriously?
Debbie, you can't just do coke
out in the open at Hamburger Hamlet.
Oh, what's the big deal?
Everybody's doing it.
It's practically a vitamin.
By the way, Steven…
I'm low.
What does it mean that my life has become
hours of laminating at Kinko's
and weekly expeditions
down to Pico to buy blow
for a commandeering little girl?
I surely deserve better.
-I want half a gram.
-[scoffs]
-Fine.
[Debbie exhales heavily]
-Scoot. Scoot.
-[Debbie scoffs]
[hostess] Wedge salad, hold the dressing.
And a loaded Reuben with thick-cut fries.
-[Susan] Thank you.
-Enjoy.
[sighs] I don't know how you stay so thin.
You look terrific, Debbie.
Just try and be happy with yourself.
I will be happy once I win Dance Off!
and everyone in this town
sees that I did it all by myself
without any help from anyone.
I won't stress. It's just some dance show.
I'm just gonna have a good time
and do my thing.
Your thing is that you win.
It's true. You win everything.
So, just don't win
this one thing for once.
I wasn't planning on it.
Don't pretend like
you aren't strategic, Susan.
God, Debbie. Where is this coming from?
You must really hate me.
You get the body, the guy,
you're gonna win homecoming queen.
In case you haven't noticed,
the new guy likes you.
-Who? Robert?
-Mm-hmm.
He doesn't like me.
For someone who looks
in the mirror all the time,
you really don't look
in the mirror, do you?
[♪ pensive music plays]
I think you need
to get some perspective, Debbie,
and take a deep breath.
I know we're best friends, Susan.
Sometimes I really could just murder you.
[♪ "Dancing with Myself" plays]
♪ On the floors of Tokyo
Or down in London town to go, go ♪
♪ With the record selection
And the mirror's reflection ♪
♪ I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪ When there's no-one else in sight
In the crowded lonely night ♪
♪ Well, I wait so long
For my love vibration ♪
♪ And I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪ Oh-oh, dancing with myself
Oh-oh-oh… ♪
[Robert]
Why isn't there a pregnant Barbie doll?
Because Ken came in another box.
[all laughing]
-Where's Thom?
-He has the flu.
Yeah, there's a serious case
of the "I can't dance" going around.
Stop it. We are here to have fun.
Well, I'm gonna win this thing
if it's the last thing I do.
Good luck with that.
♪ If I had the chance
I'd ask the world to… ♪
[Tony] Oh, oh. [laughs]
Fuck!
Cup my balls. Say my name.
Cup my balls. Say my name, say my name.
Come on. Fuck. [moans]
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. Ah.
Ah…
Holy shit.
Like Mount Saint Helens in here.
Oh. [laughs]
You're getting very good at that,
young lady.
[chuckling]
[Cha Cha] Yeah, about that…
[sniffs] Oh.
By my calculation,
and I'm getting an A in algebra,
I've given you 50 blow jobs and fucked you
six times in the past three months.
That's great. [panting] So?
So, it's time you tell
your wife about us, Tony.
Or I will.
[echoing] What?
[Debbie] I'm sorry.
This is the best we've ever looked.
I second that. [giggles]
Look at the kids. Look at the kids!
-Hi, Daddy. [chuckles]
-Wow, baby. Ooh!
-Look at you. Stunning.
-Hmm.
Bret.
-Hi.
-What's that?
[Steven] Twenty-dollar bills.
Bribes for me to give the cameramen.
That's just to assure that you get plenty
of camera time to show off your moves.
Not that you won't take
that title on your own.
Love you, Daddy.
Love you.
Um… do you wanna go practice?
[Debbie] Come on. We have got to focus.
Wow.
Look at 'em. It's all in front of them.
Because the way that you're holding me
is making me look big. Here.
I was that young once.
Yeah. During the Pleistocene era.
-Figure it out.
-Okay.
I want it all the way over there,
and then I want you to pull me in.
We're gonna go to the middle,
we're gonna do three spins…
[Debbie continues talking]
[snorting]
[shouts]
Shit.
[exhales heavily] Showtime, motherfuckers.
[announcer]
It's the first week of October 1981.
-And this is Dance Off!
-[crowd cheering]
Now, let's meet some
of this week's dancers.
Hi. I'm Bret. I like Joan Didion,
and I wanna be a writer.
[crowd applauds]
Hi. I'm Debbie,
and I'm gonna rule the world.
Hi. I'm Susan. I'd like
to pursue a career in the legal arts.
I'm Robert. I like trying new
hair products like gel and mousse
and studying the philosophies
of Kahlil Gibran.
Hi. I'm Cha Cha. I've been Groover
of the Week three months in a row,
and I'm gonna win it again tonight.
And I'm Tony Cruz, host of Dance Off!
[dancers cheering, applauding]
[Tony] All right.
This week, boy, it's an exciting one.
We're dancing down the hottest hits
in the land, featuring the Griffins.
[dancers cheering]
But first up, and new on the charts,
Rick James with "Super Freak."
-Ha ha.
-[dancers whoop]
Hit it!
[♪ "Super Freak" plays]
Fucking bitch.
♪ She's a very kinky girl ♪
♪ The kind you don't take home to mother ♪
♪ She will never let your spirits down ♪
♪ Once you get her off the street
Ow, girl ♪
♪ She likes the boys in the band ♪
♪ She says that
I'm her all-time favorite ♪
♪ When I make my move to her room
It's the right time ♪
♪ She's never hard to please
Oh, no ♪
Goddamn it. Cha Cha's got cum stains
on her blouse again.
Switch to camera two.
Fucking love Rick James,
freaky motherfucker.
[door opens]
I bring the gift of Ma Maison.
Compliments of Terry Schaffer.
Feature Debbie. Short peroxide blonde.
♪ She's all right, she's all right ♪
♪ That girl's all right with me ♪
That's her.
♪ Yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey! ♪
Have at it.
[all laughing]
♪ She's super-freaky, yow ♪
♪ Everybody sing
Super freak, super freak ♪
-♪ She's a very special girl ♪
-♪ The kind of girl you want to know ♪
-♪ From her head down to her toenails ♪
-♪ Down to her feet ♪
♪ Yeah, she'll wait for me at backstage
With her girlfriends… ♪
-♪ In a limousine ♪
-Move.
♪ Long and black and shining bright ♪
-♪ Three's not a crowd to her, she says ♪
-♪ Ménage à trois, ooh, la, la ♪
♪ "Room 714, I'll be waiting" ♪
♪ When I get there
She's got incense, wine, and candles ♪
♪ It's such a freaky scene ♪
-♪ That girl is pretty kinky ♪
-♪ The girl's a super freak ♪
-♪ The kind of girl you read about ♪
-♪ In new-wave magazines ♪
-♪ That girl is pretty wild now ♪
-♪ The girl's a super freak ♪
-♪ I really like to taste her ♪
-♪ Every time we meet ♪
♪ She's all right, she's all right ♪
♪ That girl's all right with me ♪
♪ Yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey! ♪
♪ She's a super freak, super freak
She's super-freaky, yow ♪
-♪ Temptations sing ♪
-♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
[♪ song stops]
[clock ticking]
I can dance.
I can dance. You're a good boy, Thom.
You can dance if you want to.
Even if your dad never showed you how
because he fucking left.
You can dance, goddamn it. I can dance.
[pants]
[loud ticking]
Fuck!
[objects clattering]
Fuck it!
-[bell rings]
-I'm going!
-♪ …wild now ♪
-♪ The girl's a super freak ♪
-♪ I really like to taste her ♪
-♪ Every time we meet ♪
♪ She's all right, she's all right ♪
♪ That girl's all right with me ♪
♪ Yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey! ♪
♪ She's a super freak, super freak
She's super-freaky, yow ♪
-♪ Temptations sing ♪
-♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Super freak, super freak
That girl's a super freak ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ She's a very kinky girl ♪
♪ The kind you won't take home to mother ♪
♪ And she will never
Let your spirits down ♪
♪ Once you get her off the street ♪
♪ Blow Danny ♪
[♪ saxophone playing]
♪ Oh, girl ♪
[dancers cheering]
In three, two. Throw to Tony.
That was Rick James's "Super Freak."
And today, these kids
were super freaky. Wowza.
Next up, a fantastic segment
called Ask the Kids,
Dance Off!'s Groover of the Week,
and don't touch that dial
or you might just miss
the one and only Slow Jam Romance.
I'm Tony Cruz.
I'm a Libra male,
and the party's just begun.
[cheering, applause]
[set bell rings]
[crew member] Take five, use the can,
whatever, powder your nose.
[people chattering]
Take five, powder your noses,
use the can. Whatever.
Bring it, bitch.
War's been won, Compton Heights.
Don't mess with Beverly Hills.
Anybody want a Coke?
-Oh.
-Ca-Cola.
[Debbie] Sure. Lots of ice.
-You were so, so good.
-[squeals]
-So good.
-You were so good.
[♪ eerie music plays]
[sniffs]
[Steven] Big, strapping fella like you
watching their weight?
Hi, I'm Steven.
I work for Mr. Schaffer.
Hi. Ryan.
Yeah, I know.
You run in Debbie's group.
-On the fringes.
-Ah.
[soft chuckle]
I can't eat too much sugar or I break out.
Gotta look good for the camera.
Yeah, I'm building up the courage
to get out there.
Not a very good dancer.
Au contraire, mon chéri.
You got smooth moves.
Very smooth.
[chuckles] I'm sorry,
I don't speak French too good.
[scoffs]
I always say if you can screw,
you can dance.
It's all in the pelvis. Isn't that right?
[chuckles] I don't… I don't understand.
I'm your biggest fan, Ryan.
Or is it Troy?
Troy Wad?
Yeah, see, I was the first gal on my block
to get that new device they call a VCR.
And I've seen all your movies on video.
All of them.
Horny Mommy Gang Bang.
Rusty the Lusty Pool Boy. [grunts]
That one's a classic.
-I think you might be mis--
-Mistaking you for someone else?
I don't think so.
I never forget a pretty face.
Or an even prettier ass.
Don't be ashamed, Ryan.
Pornography is the medium of the '80s.
-Oh.
-Are you threatening me?
My boss is here. Get your hands off me
or I'll cut 'em off.
[scoffs]
Everybody's got their kink. Right, Ryan?
[♪ eerie music continues]
[Terry] Looking good, kid.
[Bret] Oh.
Hi, Mr. Schaffer.
Debbie's doing so good.
Isn't she?
[inhales, sniffles]
Been kind of busy making movies out
of town for much of her high school years,
so I arranged all this
to make it up to her, I guess.
I read your treatment again last night.
Less Than a Hero.
[Bret] Less Than Zero.
Yeah.
It's very promising.
[Bret] Is it?
[Terry] Mm-hmm.
Now listen, are you Robert Towne
right now? Is this Chinatown?
No.
But it might be.
If we implement the right notes.
[Bret] Well,
writing is rewriting, right?
That's what they say
in the movie business.
That's right. [sighs]
We should meet at the Beverly Hills Hotel.
I have a nice setup there. Bungalow 2.
Debra Winger stays there
when she's in town.
[Tony] Get out!
-Get out.
-What? Why?
You told me I could have run of the place.
After you threatened to go to my wife,
ruin my life. I have three little kids.
I'll be a very good stepmother
to them, Tony. You'll see.
You're insane. You're delusional!
No, I'm not, Tony. I'm a star.
-And a star gets what she wants.
-Oh, geez.
[Cha Cha] What, you think
this is it for me?
A few more weeks of best groover,
and then what?
You lied. You know I can't afford college.
You promised you'd get me an audition
for Grease 2, and where's that?
-[grunts, sniffs]
-Anyway, I've decided
-I don't want that anymore.
-Oh, you know what?
A dancer's days are numbered in this town.
Fucking… The fuck do you think you are?
Olivia Newton-John? [panting]
Oh, my God.
You're gonna tell her, aren't you?
I don't know Olivia Newton-John,
but I'd like to.
-My wife!
-[slams table]
[panting]
And you're only 18.
You understand that
if you do this, I'm done?
I've decided I want a bigger prize, Tony.
And that prize is you.
By the way…
I'm pregnant.
What?
Little Tony Junior
is only a few months away.
I already have a kid named Tony Junior!
Then we'll call him Tony III.
[whispers] What the fuck?
Fuck.
[Tony grunts]
Tell my wife, and you're dead.
Watch your threats.
You're speaking to the mother
of your unborn child.
[tires screeching]
[♪ "Turn Me Loose" plays]
♪ I was born to run
I was born to dream ♪
♪ The craziest boy you… ♪
So, what are you gonna do
for couples dance?
I don't know. Sit this one out?
[Robert] Don't be ridiculous.
Couples dance could put you over the edge.
You could win this.
Listen, I can understand not wanting
to be homecoming queen,
but Groover of the Week?
[chuckles]
[chuckles] Come on, Susan.
Everybody wants this.
[giggles]
I do, yeah. I think I do.
[♪ wistful music plays]
During roll call…
What?
…where we said what we wanted
at the beginning.
Yeah, you said you wanted to go
into the legal arts.
-What exactly are the legal arts?
-[chuckles]
My dad wants me to be a lawyer.
My mom too.
What do you want?
I want…
I don't know.
To go off to New York City.
Get away from expectations.
I took ballet all through school,
and then last year, I just gave it up.
Maybe I want to be a professional
ballerina in a company or something.
I don't know.
You'd look very good in a tutu.
Stop it. You're making fun of me.
-Never.
-[chuckles]
Be all that you can be.
Starting right now, right here.
Win this.
Show your parents. Show them all.
I'll help you with couples dance.
You have to admit I have
some pretty sweet moves.
You do.
That you do.
[Thom] Let's do this.
[Susan chuckles]
Let's do it.
-You came.
-[Thom] Uh-huh.
[giggling]
[squeals]
[both laughing]
[Thom] Okay. [laughs]
[announcer] Who will win today's dance-off
and become Groover of the Week?
Did Dynamite Debbie do enough
to shake her way to the top?
Has Susan shown enough sass in her step
to strut off with the crown?
Or has the reigning champ, Cha Cha,
shown she has…
One vote for Cha Cha Rodriguez.
One vote for Debbie Schaffer.
She's the best contestant,
don't you think?
One vote for Susan Reynolds.
-[laughs]
-[phones ring]
One vote for Cha Cha.
That's 30 votes for Cha Cha.
Debbie Schaffer.
That's 32 votes for Debbie.
One for Susan Reynolds.
That's 34 votes for Susan Reynolds.
One for Connie Lingus.
Is she even a contestant?
[ringing]
[ringing continues]
Hello?
[heavy breathing over the phone]
[♪ suspenseful music plays]
Who is this?
-[breathing continues]
-How did you know I was here?
Who is this?
[caller] Eat it.
We need to talk.
We've had this date from the beginning.
[set bell rings]
Hey, what's up, man? You upset?
You worried about the couples dance?
I got you.
What did you say?
Well, that's why
you wanted a powwow, isn't it?
Get some tips. Here's how you do it.
Come on, imitate me. This is easy stuff.
First, just sway.
Like this. Just sway.
Do that. And then do this.
Hold her tight. Just sway.
Like this.
Press your inevitably swelling dick
into her.
Swear to God she'll get wet and
you'll feel it right through her dress.
Hey, let go. What's your deal, man?
Just stop. Stop what you're doing.
What am I doing?
Waltzing into my school
and flirting with my girl under my nose
like I'm not even there, pretending
like you're the big man on campus.
-And that's your role, am I right?
-Yeah, that's right. I'm the quarterback.
You're nothing. You're weird.
You're too cool for school,
and that shit stops today.
-Does it?
-Yeah, it does.
So what? You're worldly.
You've been to Europe.
I see how you look at Susan.
I saw you talking to her way too sexy-like
when I walked in this place.
And I was kind to you.
I said to everybody,
"Be nice to the new kid. Let him in."
Now I'm telling you to your smug
little face, you're not so nice.
I know you're not. I see you.
Wipe off that flop sweat.
Just knock it off, man! There's something
seriously wrong with you!
As of today, this dynamic with Susan,
with me, it ends!
Smoke?
Okay, Thom, as you calm
your clearly agitated nervous system
after a complete evisceration
of my character,
let me hold up a mirror to you.
Can you handle that?
Yeah, I can handle that.
I think you're a scared little boy.
Deep down inside, you know you peaked
in high school and you're terrified.
You're looking for a villain
to blame in your story
for your inevitable psychic collapse,
but it won't be me.
I won't accept it. Blame somebody else.
Maybe your father.
It's suddenly clear to me
why he abandoned you.
Because you're fucking worthless.
And needy.
An embarrassment of a man,
and no father wants that.
Watch your mouth.
Or better yet, do the easy thing
and blame Susan for being drawn to me.
Maybe she's tired of living
in your fake, tarnished, tinsel cage.
Maybe your adenoidal jock allure is fading
as you age out.
Or maybe, just maybe,
someone needs to do just this:
break everyone
out of your spell of mediocrity.
Do you see me?
'Cause I see you,
and I don't like what I see.
You're a weak flatline of a person.
And maybe what Susan needs,
what everyone in this group needs,
is someone like me.
A goddamn jolt
of adrenaline and leadership.
I'll see you in there, buddy.
Or not.
-[set bell rings]
-[snorting]
[crewmember 1] We're live in ten.
Tony to set, please. Tony to set.
[crewmember 2] Seven, six…
-[Tony] I can fucking count.
-…five, four…
-Where's Thom and Robert?
-I don't know.
-…three, two…
-I know how to fucking count.
I just need you to help me with who's who.
And we're back. How's everyone
feeling so far? How's everybody doing?
[cheering]
It's great to hear.
Your crew's moves are fantastic today.
All right, everybody watching at home.
Coming up, we have the crowning
of the Groover of the Week.
And let me tell you,
after the tally I just saw,
this week is a squeaker.
Also coming up is my personal favorite,
Slow Jam Romance.
But now a fan favorite segment,
Ask the Kids.
And we have our next caller.
-Caller, what's your name?
-Connect line two.
-Where are you calling from?
-Hi, I'm Daphne.
I'm a junior at Brentwood,
and my question is for Cha Cha.
-[Cha Cha gasps]
-Cha Cha, we all know you can really move.
Is that what you want to pursue
when you graduate, a career as a dancer?
Actually, no.
And, Daphne, thanks for calling.
My goal is to win today, so vote for me.
[laughs]
But ultimately, what I really want is
to be a wife and a mother.
-[dancers] Aww.
-Next caller. [chuckles]
Line four is live.
[caller 2] Bonjour, my name is Violet.
[in French accent] I am a sophomore
exchange student from… [babbles]
[Tony] Violet, you're a little muffled.
Try talking into the receiver.
Who was your question for?
Yes, sorry.
My question is for Ryan.
Ryan, you seem so familiar.
Where have I seen you before? [gasps]
Were you an extra or something or, mmm…
Pardon. What was the name of that movie?
Porky's?
Uh, hi, um…
-[Tony] Cat got your tongue, Ryan?
-[dancers laughing]
No, I'm…
This is my first time
in front of a camera…
today.
Fantastique.
Well, you've got star quality.
Keep shining bright.
[chuckles softly]
[Tony] And that he does.
I mean, all of these kids from California
just have that special sauce
that we're seeing on full display
here on Dance Off!,
the most awesome
boogie-down show ever created.
-[laughing]
-Next caller.
[caller 3]
Hi. This is Paul from Campbell Hall.
Yes, hi, Paul.
Tell me, who's your question for?
My question's for Debbie.
It's really more of an opinion, really.
But you…
I voted for you, and, uh,
I hope you know a lot of people
are rooting for you and, uh…
[fake sobs, sniffles]
You deserve something nice.
You deserve to win.
Daddy?
-Is this guy crying?
-We got ourselves a Mama Rose.
[panting]
[grunts] Motherfucker! You fuck…
Goddamn it! Sick! Sick! Sick! Sick!
[nervous chuckle]
I think we only got time for one more.
-Got a live one on line five.
-Connected.
[chuckles] Caller, what's your question,
and who's it for?
-[heavy breathing on the phone]
-[static crackles]
I did it. [heavy breathing continues] I…
[Tony] Caller, what's your question?
Look inside, inside this world.
Caller, you're on the air.
[screaming on the phone]
[dancers groan]
-[moans]
-[line disconnects, dial tone]
[Tony chuckles]
Say something, dickwad!
Throw to the next segment!
[chortles] Boys and girls,
that is the magic of live television.
[dancers laugh]
All right, now on to the next segment.
Are you ready, kids?
-[cheering]
-This is Slow Jam Romance.
[♪ "Waiting for a Girl Like You" plays]
Can you pull me in?
Sex it up a little bit?
This is my moment.
Please help me win this.
I am.
You're not.
For once in this relationship,
pretend to feel something, goddamn it.
I want you to win this. I do.
♪ It feels so right, so warm and true ♪
♪ I need to know if you feel it too ♪
♪ Maybe I'm wrong
Won't you tell me… ♪
Kiss me.
I don't think it's that kind--
♪ This heart of mine
Has been hurt before ♪
♪ This time I want be be sure ♪
♪ I've been waiting for a girl like you ♪
♪ To come into my life ♪
-♪ I've been waiting for a girl like you ♪
-♪ Waiting for a… ♪
The voters are gonna love this.
-Good for her.
-[chuckles]
-♪ I've been waiting for someone new ♪
-♪ Waiting ♪
♪ To make me feel alive ♪
-♪ Yeah, waiting for a girl like you ♪
-♪ Waiting for a girl ♪
♪ To come into my life ♪
[Cha Cha] Wanna dance?
Not really.
The caller says you have star quality,
so let's show them what you can do.
♪ You're so good ♪
Excuse me, guys.
♪ When we make love it's understood ♪
♪ It's more than a touch
Or a word we say ♪
♪ When you love someone ♪
♪ Now, I know it's right ♪
♪ From the moment I wake up
Till deep in the night… ♪
-Boo!
-[shrieks]
What are you doing?
I just wanna dance
with the prettiest girl in school.
Thom's not here.
♪ I've been waiting ♪
Come on. Let's go.
♪ For a girl like you ♪
♪ To come into my life ♪
-♪ I've been waiting for a girl like you ♪
-♪ Waiting for a ♪
♪ A love that will survive ♪
-♪ I've been waiting for someone new ♪
-♪ Waiting ♪
♪ To make me feel alive ♪
-♪ Yeah, waiting for a girl like you ♪
-♪ Waiting, waiting for a girl ♪
♪ To come into my life ♪
♪ I've been waiting ♪
♪ Waiting for you ♪
♪ Ooh… ♪
This feels wrong.
No, this feels right.
♪ I've been waiting ♪
♪ I've been waiting for a girl like you ♪
♪ Won't you come into my life? ♪
[♪ vocalizing]
Debbie is so crazy about Bret.
[♪ "Angel of the Morning" plays]
I just don't want her to get hurt.
I've hurt her enough already, you know?
All the shitty things I've done…
I just don't want
anybody to hurt her anymore.
You've done too much coke today.
I've got a quaalude in the car.
I can dance.
Better get the lead out, you big lug.
New kid in town's bumping privates
with your girlfriend.
[♪ "Angel of the Morning" continues,
muffled]
[Thom grunts]
What the fuck?
[Susan] You guys, stop it!
Thom, look at me. Thom!
-Go to commercial!
-[Susan] Enough!
-Are you kidding? This is ratings gold.
-Cut to camera three!
I'll kill you! [grunts]
[Susan] I said enough!
Enough!
-No, no, no, no, no.
-[Susan] Stop! Robert!
You better go break this up, big guy.
[Susan] Enough! I said enough!
-[both grunting]
-Go to commercial!
Pussy.
[man on TV] Make your meals sing with…
-[Thom grunts] I'll kill you!
-[Susan] I said enough!
Robert! I said enough!
[Tony] This is… This is not…
This is not what we do in show business!
-[Terry] No, no! No, no, no.
-Do something!
Thom, Thom.
[♪ tense music plays]
[cameraperson] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's okay, I promise.
Hey, your hair looks great today.
I am humiliated.
Consider yourself lucky.
I wish I had two guys fighting over me.
[chuckles softly] Come on.
Let's go to the makeup station
and get you touched up, okay?
-[Susan sniffles]
-This fluorescent lighting is shit.
Hey, Debbie.
I hope that you win.
I hope I win too.
[both chuckle]
-[sighs] Slut.
-Whore.
[toilet flushing]
[door open, closes]
-[lock clicks]
-[light footsteps]
Hello?
[♪ tense music plays]
[footsteps continue]
[water running]
[door creaks]
[screaming]
[crewmember] Everyone to set, please.
We're back in 30. We're back in 30.
[Bret] You know, I think you got this.
-Celebrate with a powdered doughnut?
-[chuckles]
-You can snort the sugar off it.
-[scoffs] Funny.
I can't. My diet.
Hey, you were great out there.
You're sexy and great.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. [chuckles]
Took my breath away.
I love you.
[crewmember] Fifteen seconds until
Groover of the Week. Fifteen seconds.
Here we go.
-Oh.
-[set bell rings]
-Ten seconds until--
-I got it. I got it. Fuck!
Debbie. Where's Cha Cha?
Where's Cha Cha?
[scoffs] Probably left when she felt
she was about to get skunked.
And we're live in four, three…
[mouthing] Two, one.
That about wraps it up
for this week's episode of Dance Off!
-How about it, Senior Class?
-[cheering]
Do you ever wish you could go back,
start all over?
[dancers cheering, applauding]
Be young again?
I'd kill for that opportunity.
Now, as always,
the moment we've all been waiting for,
this week's Groover of the Week.
[contestant] Whoo!
The Groover of the Week is…
Drumroll, please.
Hit snare sound effect.
[drumroll]
By a landslide, Susan Reynolds!
[cheering]
Congratulations.
Susan, congrats!
[dancers whistling, applauding]
[Tony] Congratulations. By a landslide.
[♪ dramatic music plays]
[cheering continues]
[Tony] Congrats.
[Tony] Susan Reynolds.
-[streamers popping]
-All right!
[cheering continues]
There's always next year.
She won't be
in high school next year, Steven.
I don't know.
Let's end this shebang with a bang!
This is "Just Can't Get Enough"
by Depeche Mode.
[cheering]
[♪ "Just Can't Get Enough" plays]
-[Terry] Baby--
-No, this is because of you!
I'll talk to her.
Debbie, wait.
Debbie, wait, it's okay.
[crying] Please leave me alone.
It's okay. Wait. Debbie, wait!
[sighs]
-[Debbie screams] Bret! Bret!
-Shit.
-What?
-Look.
[♪ ominous music plays]
[Debbie grunts]
[creaking]
[Debbie] Oh, my God. [gasps]
[♪ "Just Can't Get Enough" continues]
♪ We walk together
We're walking down the street ♪
♪ And I just can't get enough
And I just can't get enough ♪
♪ Every time I think of you
I know we have to meet ♪
♪ And I just can't get enough
And I just can't get enough ♪
♪ It's getting hotter
It's a burning love ♪
♪ And I just can't seem to get enough of ♪
[chuckles]
♪ I just can't get enough
I just can't get enough ♪
♪ I just can't get enough… ♪
[♪ music stops]
[breathes shakily]
Did I miss the party?
[♪ "Just Can't Get Enough" continues]
♪ I just can't get enough
I just can't get enough ♪
♪ And when it rains
You're shining down for me ♪
♪ And I just can't get enough
And I just can't get enough ♪
♪ Just like a rainbow
You know you set me free ♪
♪ And I just can't get enough
And I just can't get enough ♪
♪ You're like an angel
And you give me your love ♪
♪ And I just can't seem to get enough of ♪
♪ I just can't get enough
I just can't get enough ♪